(record needle scratching)
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ You should know, you
should know that, ah ♪
♪ Kris Kross is not
having anything today ♪
♪ As we stand there totally crossed out ♪
♪ We commence to make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Don't try to compare us
to another bad little fad ♪
♪ I'm the Mac and I'm bad ♪
♪ Givin' you something
that you never had ♪
♪ I'll make you bump bump,
wiggle and shake your rump ♪
♪ 'Cause I be kicking the flavor
that makes you wanna jump ♪
♪ How high, real high,
'cause I'm just so fly ♪
♪ A young lovable, huggable type of guy ♪
♪ And everything is to the
back with a little slack ♪
♪ 'Cause inside out is wiggida,
wiggida, wiggida wack ♪
♪ I come stompin' with somethin'
pumpin' to keep you jumpin' ♪
♪ R&B, rappin' bull crap
is what I'm dumpin' ♪
♪ Ain't nothin' sucker 'bout
Kris Kross, we all that ♪
♪ So when they ask, do they rock ♪
♪ Say, believe that ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Uh huh, uh huh ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ I like my stuff knockin' ♪
♪ Knockin' ♪
♪ I love it when a
girlies be like jockin' ♪
♪ Jockin' ♪
♪ The D-A-double D-Y-M-A-C ♪
♪ Yeah, you know me ♪
♪ I got you jumpin' and
bumpin' and pumpin' ♪
♪ Movin' all around, G ♪
♪ In the mix, I made MCs step back ♪
♪ They try to step to the
Mac, then they got jacked ♪
♪ To the back you'll
be sportin' the gear ♪
♪ Is that coincidental ♪
♪ Act like you know it, don't
be claiming that it's mental ♪
♪ Two lil' kids with a
flow you ain't ever heard ♪
♪ And nothin' fake, you
can understand every word ♪
♪ As you listen to my
cool, smooth melody ♪
♪ The Daddy makes you J-U-M-P ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Uh huh, uh huh ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Now, the formalities of this and that ♪
♪ Is that Kris Kross
ain't comin' off wack ♪
♪ And for all y'all
suckers that don't know ♪
♪ Check it out ♪
♪ Some of them try to rhyme but
they can't rhyme like this ♪
♪ Some of them try to
rhyme but they can't ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the ♪
♪ miggida, miggida,
miggida, miggida Mac Daddy ♪
♪ The miggida, miggida,
miggida, miggida Mac ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the ♪
♪ Miggida, miggida,
miggida, miggida Mac Daddy ♪
♪ The miggida, miggida,
miggida, miggida Mac ♪
♪ I make you wanna ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Uh huh, uh huh ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Uh huh, uh huh ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Uh huh, uh huh ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ The Mac Dad'll make you ♪
♪ Daddy Mac'll make you ♪
♪ Jump, jump ♪
♪ Kris Kross'll make you ♪
♪ Believe that ♪
(hip-hop music)